# Nate Iske

# **Sound Designer**

#### Nate Iske

Website: https://taiga.audio/

Phone: 815.721.7391

Email: nate@taiga.audio

## Summary

6 years of experience across game development, film, commercial, music, and museum installations.

Credited as a sound designer on 3 shipped AAA titles.

Led the audio development for multiple independent games.

Experienced with proprietary tools, Wwise, FMOD, Unity, Unreal, Reaper, Pro Tools, Nuendo, Sound Forge, Perforce, and Premiere.

Mixed within a 5.1 environment in both games and film.

Familiar with various recorders, microphones, and recording techniques.

# **Experience**

### Taiga Audio / Owner / Sound Designer

Dec 2019 - Present

Conducted all business aspects and game audio development for various projects ranging from AAA to indie.

#### DICE LA (Electronic Arts) / Audio Artist I - Audio Artist II

Aug 2017 - Dec 2019, Los Angeles, California

Recorded and designed assets for weapon fire, weapon reloads, gadgets, and quad ambiences. Implemented work into Frostbite.

Set up animation tags in EA's proprietary animation program.

#### **Vixen Productions / Sound Designer**

Jan 2014 - Aug 2017, Rockford, Illinois

Led all sound-related tasks for narrative, corporate and live events (100+ projects).

Tasked with dialogue editing, sound editing, recording, and sound design.

#### Rock Valley College / Production Assistant (Audio Specialist)

Jan 2014 - Aug 2017, Rockford, Illinois

Trouble-shot audio and technical issues for the Mass Communications studio. Assisted students with audio hardware, software, and concepts.

#### **Education**

**Vancouver Film School** / Diploma with Honours, Sound Design for Visual Media

2016 - 2017, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada

Collaborated as the sound designer for student films and games. Mixed various projects in a Dobly Digital 5.1 theater.

Rock Valley College / Mass Communications (Audio Focused)

2014 - 2015, Rockford, Illinois

Recorded and mixed radio interviews, radio ads, live television, and live music. Sound designed across multiple student films.

# **Highlighted Projects**

Battlefield 1 / Sound Designer / DICE LA

Battlefield V / Sound Designer / DICE LA

Godfall / Sound Designer / Taiga Audio

Battlefield 1: Apocalypse / Sound Designer / DICE LA

Battlefield 1: Turning Tides / Sound Designer / DICE LA

**Battlefield 1: In The Name Of The Tsar** / Sound Designer / DICE LA

Battlefield V: Firestorm / Sound Designer / DICE LA

Rogue Legacy 2 / Sound Designer / Taiga Audio

Freedom Finger / Sound Designer / Taiga Audio

#### **Awards**

AVA Digital Award / Rock House Kids Video

Best Game / Vancouver Film School / Drift Kings

**Most Intriguing Game** / Ayzenberg's Holo Lens Game Jam / Chef Simulator

**Top 10 Nomination** / Film Racing's International Film Festival

**Best Drama Short Nomination** / Genre Celebration Festival / Sentience

**Best Trailer** / Red Corner Film Festival / Sentience